<?xml version="1.0"?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>1.00</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to dissemminate information to anyone interested in their software products.  To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
<Company_Info>
        <Company_Name>C. Ghisler &amp; Co.</Company_Name>
        <Address_1>P.O. Box</Address_1>
        <Address_2 />
        <City_Town>Bolligen</City_Town>
        <State_Province />
        <Zip_Postal_Code>CH-3065</Zip_Postal_Code>
        <Country>Switzerland</Country>
        <ASP_Member>Y</ASP_Member>
        <ASP_Member_Number>03698</ASP_Member_Number>
        <ESC_Member>N</ESC_Member>
        <Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.ghisler.com/</Company_WebSite_URL>
<Contact_Info>
        <Author_First_Name>Christian</Author_First_Name>
        <Author_Last_Name>Ghisler</Author_Last_Name>
        <Author_Email>support@ghisler.com</Author_Email>
        <Contact_First_Name>Christian</Contact_First_Name>
        <Contact_Last_Name>Ghisler</Contact_Last_Name>
        <Contact_Email>support@ghisler.com</Contact_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
<Support_Info>
        <Sales_Email>sales@ghisler.com</Sales_Email>
        <Support_Email>support@ghisler.com</Support_Email>
        <General_Email>support@ghisler.com</General_Email>
        <Sales_Phone />
        <Support_Phone />
        <General_Phone />
        <Fax_Phone />
    </Support_Info>
</Company_Info>
<Program_Info>
        <Program_Name>Windows Commander</Program_Name>
        <Program_Version>4.51</Program_Version>
        <Program_Release_Month>07</Program_Release_Month>
        <Program_Release_Day>18</Program_Release_Day>
        <Program_Release_Year>2000</Program_Release_Year>
        <Program_Cost_Dollars>28</Program_Cost_Dollars>
        <Program_Cost_Other>CHF 40</Program_Cost_Other>
        <Program_Type>Shareware</Program_Type>
        <Program_Release_Status>Minor Update</Program_Release_Status>
        <Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
        <Program_OS_Support>Win95,Win98,WinNT 4.x,Windows2000</Program_OS_Support>
        <Program_Language>English,Dutch,French,German,Italian,Spanish</Program_Language>
        <Program_System_Requirements>Pentium class or faster processor</Program_System_Requirements>
        <Program_Categories>Explorer replacements, File managers, File utilties, Disk utilities</Program_Categories>
<File_Info>
        <Filename_Versioned>wc32v451.zip</Filename_Versioned>
        <Filename_Previous>wc32v450.zip</Filename_Previous>
        <Filename_Generic>wincmd32.zip</Filename_Generic>
        <Filename_Long>wincmd32.zip</Filename_Long>
        <File_Size_Bytes>1245410</File_Size_Bytes>
        <File_Size_K>1216</File_Size_K>
        <File_Size_MB>1.22</File_Size_MB>
    </File_Info>
<Expire_Info>
        <Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
        <Expire_Count />
        <Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
        <Expire_Other_Info />
        <Expire_Month />
        <Expire_Day />
        <Expire_Year />
    </Expire_Info>
        <Includes_VB_Runtime>N</Includes_VB_Runtime>
        <Includes_JAVA_VM>N</Includes_JAVA_VM>
        <Includes_DirectX>N</Includes_DirectX>
</Program_Info>
<Program_Descriptions>
<English>
        <Keywords>Windows Commander file manager explorer replacement two windows</Keywords>
        <Char_Desc_45>Windows Commander 4.51 32bit fileman/archiver</Char_Desc_45>
        <Char_Desc_80>Windows Commander 4.51 32bit Explorer replacement, ZIP manager and FTP client</Char_Desc_80>
        <Char_Desc_250>Wincmd is a file manager replacement for Windows 9x and Windows NT.
Features: Drag&amp;Drop from and to explorer/desktop. Packer shell for
ZIP/ARJ/LHA/RAR/UC2/TAR/GZ/CAB/ACE. Command line, full text
search also in packed files, button bar, FTP client.</Char_Desc_250>
        <Char_Desc_450>Wincmd is a file manager replacement for Windows 9x and Windows NT.
Features: Drag&amp;Drop from and to explorer/desktop. Packer shell for
ZIP/ARJ/LHA/RAR/UC2/TAR/GZ/CAB/ACE. Command line, full text
search also in packed files, button bar.  Supports 14 languages.
FTP client, access to Network Neighborhood, Uuencode/Decode,
compare by content, synchronize dirs.</Char_Desc_450>
        <Char_Desc_2000>Windows Commander  is an Explorer  replacement  for  Windows.
This is the 32 bit version for Windows 95/98 and Windows NT.
A 16 bit version is also available as wc16v451.zip.
Windows Commander  handles archives  like  subdirectories. It
supports ZIP/ARJ/LHA/RAR/UC2/TAR/GZ/CAB/ACE archives, and has
an internal ZIP-compatible packer. The search function allows
to search for files inside archives, even for text. A command
line helps starting  programs  with parameters,  and a  fully
configurable button bar allows to launch  programs and inter-
nal  commands.  The built-in  viewer can show files  in text,
hex, binary, image and multimedia format.  The 32 bit version
supports Drag&amp;Drop  from and to  explorer/desktop,  delete to
the recycle bin,  and Explorer  style context  menus/property
sheets.  FTP servers  on the  Internet  can be accessed  like
local drives.  A configurable directory  hotlist  (bookmarks)
and history list make directory  navigation easier.  The sync
function allows to  synchronize two complete directory trees,
and the compare function  shows the  difference of two binary
or text files highlighted side by side. The new parallel port
connection works between any combination of Windows 95/98/ME,
Windows NT 4, and Windows 2000.

Homepage: http://www.ghisler.com

Special requirements: None.

Changes: 4.51 is a maintenance release.
         4.50 adds many enhancements. The most important are
         a PC to PC link over a parallel port cable, a special
         rename tool, and colors by file type.</Char_Desc_2000>
</English>
<German>
        <Keywords>Datei: Packer / Backup, Datei: Utilities, Dateimanager, Explorer-Ersatz</Keywords>
        <Char_Desc_45>Windows Commander 4.51 32bit Dateimanager</Char_Desc_45>
        <Char_Desc_80>Windows Commander 4.51 32bit Dateimanager/Explorer-Ersatz, FTP-Client</Char_Desc_80>
        <Char_Desc_250 />
        <Char_Desc_450 />
        <Char_Desc_2000 />
</German>
</Program_Descriptions>
<Web_Info>
<Application_URLs>
        <Application_Info_URL>http://www.ghisler.com/</Application_Info_URL>
        <Application_Order_URL>http://www.ghisler.com/order.htm</Application_Order_URL>
        <Application_Screenshot_URL>http://www.ghisler.com/picture.htm</Application_Screenshot_URL>
        <Application_Icon_URL>http://www.ghisler.com/wincmd.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
        <Application_XML_File_URL>http://www.ghisler.com/padinfo/wincmd32.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
<Download_URLs>
        <Primary_Download_URL>ftp://ftp.cdrom.com/pub/simtelnet/win95/diskutl/wc32v451.zip</Primary_Download_URL>
        <Secondary_Download_URL>ftp://ftp.demon.co.uk/pub/simtelnet/win95/diskutl/wc32v451.zip</Secondary_Download_URL>
        <Additional_Download_URL_1>ftp://mirrors.aol.com/pub/simtelnet/win95/diskutl/wc32v451.zip</Additional_Download_URL_1>
        <Additional_Download_URL_2>http://oak.oakland.edu/pub/simtelnet/win95/diskutl/wc32v451.zip</Additional_Download_URL_2>
    </Download_URLs>
</Web_Info>
<Permissions>
        <Distribution_Permissions>The Shareware version may be freely distributed on the Internet, on CD-ROM
or on disks, provided that
- the original files inside the distribution zip file are not modified
- the program isn&apos;t bundled with illegal or offensive material
- the Shareware isn&apos;t sold or promoted as being the registered or full product
Differing conditions need to be negotiated. E-mail: support@ghisler.com</Distribution_Permissions>
        <EULA>Software Licence / Copyright

Software Licence

Please read the following lines carefully before using this software. If you disagree with any of
the following, you are not allowed to use this program. You MUST then delete it immediately.

Shareware-version

You have the right to test this program for a period of one month. You are allowed to copy this Shareware
version (and ONLY the Shareware version) and give it to any other person, as long as it is not modified in
any way. Under modifications is understood the changing, adding or removing of any files of this package
without the author&apos;s written permission. You are NOT allowed to pack this program together with a
commercial program or a book. Shareware dealers are allowed to sell the Shareware version for a small
fee (around CHF/US$ 10.-). You are encouraged to put this program on as many BBS systems as possible.
The distribution on CD-ROM is also permitted, as long as the original files are not changed in any way. 
Please contact me if you want to distribute the program with a different installation program, changed files etc.

Use of this software after the trial period of one month is in violation of international Copyright law! It is also
unfair to the author, who has spent hundreds of hours developing this program.

Registration

This program is neither freeware nor public domain. Use after the 30 day trial period requires registration.
The registration fee is currently only CHF 40.- incl. S&amp;H ($ 28.- US personal cheque or cash including
handling fees) for a personal licence. See the help file for details on registration and support.

Registered version (personal licence)

The registered version may be installed on as many computers as desired, as long as it is ONLY running on
one at any one time (I.e. one installation at home and one at the office used by the same person). The
usage by multiple people at the same time (on multiple computers) requires additional licences.

Additional licences (multi-user licences)

Additional licences allow an institution, company or school to install the program on multiple computers or on
a server. It must be guaranteed that the program does not run on more machines at the same time than there
are licences purchased. All licences are issued to the same (company) name, which appears in the program&apos;s
title bar. Additional licences cost CHF 20.- for the 2nd to 10th licence, etc. (see help file for details).
For larger amounts than 1000 please contact the author. Each additional licence also allows a single user to
use the program at home.

Liability

We try to keep our software as bug-free as possible. But it&apos;s a general rule (Murphy&apos;s), that no software ever
is error free, and the number of errors increases with the complexity of the program. That&apos;s why we cannot
guarantee that this software will run in every environment, on any Windows compatible machine, together
with any other application, without producing errors. Any liability for damage of any sort is hereby denied. In
any case, the liability is limited to the registration fee.

Please test this program with non-critical data. We cannot guarantee the safety of your data. Especially new
operating systems like Windows NT or OS/2 can cause trouble. Should you detect errors before registration,
you accept them if you register. Any description of bugs will be accepted, but we cannot guarantee that we
will be able to correct them.

All mentioned Trademarks and Copyrights belong to their respective owners.

Legal domicile is Bern, Switzerland.

Christian Ghisler, C. Ghisler &amp; Co., PO Box, CH-3065 Bolligen, Switzerland, 2000</EULA>
</Permissions>
<MSN>
    <MSN_FORM>Y</MSN_FORM>
    <MSN_IS_32bit>Y</MSN_IS_32bit>
</MSN>
<ZDNET>
    <ZDNET_FORM>Y</ZDNET_FORM>
    <ZDNET_Product_ID_Code />
</ZDNET>
<DeuPAD>
    <DeuPAD_Extension_Version>1.00</DeuPAD_Extension_Version>
    <DeuPAD_Extension_Info>For information on the DeuPAD Extensions please go to http://www.o-grahl.de/deupad/</DeuPAD_Extension_Info>
    <SAVE_Member>N</SAVE_Member>
    <SAVE_Member_Number />
    <Company_Unique_ID />
    <Program_Cost_EUR />
    <Program_Cost_DEM />
    <Save_Prog_Num />
    <Program_Unique_ID />
    <Program_Categories_German />
    <Program_System_Requirements_German />
    <Expire_Other_Info_German />
    <EULA_German />
</DeuPAD>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
